Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 544 records
1930-2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0051
80 Linear Feet
This collection contains records created by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544. Included are correspondence, meeting minutes and agendas, working agreements and drafts, personnel and grievance records, handbooks, constitutions, by-laws, rosters, ledgers, brochures and pamphlets, photographs, and ephemera. The material dates from 1930-2013.
Biographical / Historical
Local 544 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters is located in Minnesota. It was chartered in 1936. The leaders of 544 went on to develop the area and conference bargaining that exists today in the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. It has merged with other Locals throughout the years, including Local 120 in 1998.
Arrangement
Organized into 5 series: Working Agreements and Related Correspondence; Grievance Records; Company Records; Teamster Records; Ephemera.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2013 [2013.021]
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, meeting minutes and agendas, working agreements and drafts, personnel and grievance records, handbooks, constitutions, by-laws, rosters, ledgers, brochures and pamphlets, photographs, and ephemera. The material dates from 1930-2013. These are the records of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544, located in Minnesota.
Correspondence; Labor; Labor unions
- Working Agreements and Related Correspondence, Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  The materials of this series include finalized working agreements, drafts, and related correspondence. They range in date from 1952-2013. These materials represent the negotiations and end results of developing working agreements between various companies and the Teamsters.
  Arrangement
  Folders in this series are arranged alphabetically by the name of the company.
  - 14 Transport Company, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AG Processing, Incorporated, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ANR Freight System, Incorporated, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abraham Transfer, 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ace Alkire Freight Lines, Incorporated, undated; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Ace Lines, Incorporated [1/2], 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ace Lines, Incorporated [2/2], 1973-1978; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agora Distribution, Incorporated, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ahmann Transfer, 1963-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Air Express International Corporation [1/2], 1973-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Air Express International Corporation [2/2], 1980-1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allied Automotive Group, 1995-1999; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Allied Storage Warehouse Corporation, 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Allstate Transportation Company, 1977-1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Bakeries, 1987-1991; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Food Service Supply, 1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - American Flexible Conduit, Division of Nortek, Incorporated, 1978-1981; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - American Freight Systems, Incorporated, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Linen Supply Company, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Amherst H. Wilder Foundation, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Applied Texture, Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Armour and Company [1/3], 1970-1978; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Armour and Company [2/3], 1978-1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Armour and Company [3/3], 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arrow Motor Freight, 1969-1979; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aslesens Company [1/2], 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Aslesens Company [2/2], 1965-1989; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Associated Milk Producers, Incorporated, 1986-1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Atlas Plastics Corporation [1/2], 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Atlas Plastics Corporation [2/2], 1981-1985; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - August Deike Transfer, 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Banquet Foods Corporation, 1974-1985; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Barber Transportation Company, 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Barrett Moving and Storage, 1979-2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bay and Bay Transfer Company, 1981-1985; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Beatrice Meats, Incorporated/Swift-Eckrich, 1971-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Beaver Transport Company, 1967-1970; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bell Cold Storage Company, 1973-1985; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Beltmann North American Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ben Dieke Transfer and Storage, Incorporated, 1976-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ben Franklin Drivers, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ben Franklin Stores, Incorporated, 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Ben Neitage, George E. Carlstrom, Robert W. Carlstrom, Eric A. Carlstrom, Oscar Kulseth Construction Companies, 1963-1969; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Berger Transfer and Storage Company/Berger Ready Mix Concrete, 1966-2004; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bergin Wholesale Fruit Company, 1979-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bergold Properties, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bix Fruit Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bloomington Cartage and Delivery Service, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Boyd Transfer and Storage Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Brainerd Recreational Supply, Division of Bangor Punta Corporation, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Brede Convention Drayage, 1982; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Briggs Transportation Company, 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bringgold Meat Company, Abrams Meat Distributors, Schumacher Wholesale Meats, Ellison's Wholsale Meat Company, Heinbackel Produce Company, 1976-1978; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brokers Warehouse, Incorporated, 1958-1959; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Burlington-Northern Air Freight, Incorporated [1/2], 1978-1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Burlington-Northern Air Freight, Incorporated [2/2], 1985-1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Butler Aviation - Minneapolis, Incorporated, 1988-1992; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Campbell Soup Company [1/7], 1960-1978; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Campbell Soup Company [2/7], 1977-1981; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Campbell Soup Company [3/7], 1981-1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Campbell Soup Company [4/7], 1986-1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Campbell Soup Company [5/7], 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Campbell Soup Company [6/7], 1991-1994; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Campbell Soup Company [7/7], 1994-1997; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Capp Homes, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Carpenter Transfer, Incorporated, 1974-1982; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cartage Employers' Management Association, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Casey Hoban Transfer Company, 1967-1970; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ceco Steel, 1976-1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Central Health Care of Lecenter, Incorporated, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Central States Area Iron and Steel and Special Commodity [1/3], 1967-1979; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Central States Area Iron and Steel and Special Commodity [2/3], 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Central States Area Iron and Steel and Special Commodity [3/3], 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Central States Area Local Cartage Agreement [1/2], 1967-1998; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Central States Area Local Cartage Agreement [2/2], 1963-1979; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Central States Area Over-the-Road Agreement [1/2], 1961-1979; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Central States Area Over-the-Road Agreement [2/2], 1976-1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Central States Area Tank Truck Agreement, 1970-1989; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Century Motor Freight, Incorporated, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Champion International Corporation, 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Avenue Transfer, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chippewa Springs Corporation, 1961-1982; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Churchill Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Circle 7 Moving, 1967-1970; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - City of St. Paul, 1980-1982; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - City of Worthington [1/2], 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - City of Worthington [2/2], 1983-1991; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - City Dray Line, Incorporated, 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Clark Transport Company, Incorporated, 1975-1979; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Baking Company, Division of Campbell Taggart Baking Companies, Incorporated, 1994-1997; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commerce Freight Terminals, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - ConAgra Frozen Food Company, 1980-1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Concord Beverage Company, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Concrete Minnesota, Incorporated, 1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Connolly Cartage Company, 1982; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Consolidated Freightways, Incorporated, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Continental Minnesota, Incorporated, 1976-1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Continental Minnesota, Salad Ready Division, 1976-1980; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cotter and Company, 1977-1982; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - County of Nobles [1/3], 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - County of Nobles [2/3], 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - County of Nobles [3/3], 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Culligan Water Conditioning Company, 1977-1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Creamette Company, 1960-1982; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Crouse Cartage Company, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - D.J.W. Cartage, 1974; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Dahlen Transport, 1970-1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Day Distributing Company, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dayton's, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Delivery Management Services, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Dick Beverage Company, Incorporated, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Don Ekelund Coffee Company, 1966-1973; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Donaldson's, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Driver Power, Incorporated, 1979; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Drivers Service, Incorporated, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Dry Storage Agreement, 1977-1980; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - E.L. Murphy Trucking Company, 1971-1979; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - E.S.B., Incorporated, 1977-1983; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - East Side Beverage Company, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Edex, Incoporated, 1989-1994; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Edgecomb Metals Company, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Elk River Concrete Products Company, 1977-1985; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Elmore Concrete Products Company, 1974-1983; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Emery Air Freight Corporation [1/2], 1977-1982; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Emery Air Freight Corporation [2/2], 1982-1988; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - F.H. Bathke Company, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - F.H. Peavey and Company, 1975-1982; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fairmont Community Hospital, 1994-1996; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Famous Foods, 1979; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Farmland Soy Processing Company, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Farnquist Dray and Transfer/Johnson Transfer, Incorporated, 1964-1981; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Firestone, 1975-1987; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Fisher Transfer and Moving Company, 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Fitzgerald Transfer, Incorporated, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Flamingo Hilton Corporation, 1989-1994; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Fleet Delivery, 1975; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Frank's Transfer, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Fred Asche Transfer/ Van Ort Moving and Storage, 1964-1979; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Fresh Pack, Incorporated, Division of H. Brooks and Company, 1976-1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Fresh Pack, Incorporated, 1974-1978; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Fullerton Metals Company, 1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Furnco Warehouse, Incorporated, 1967-1979; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - G.M.W., Incorporated, 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Gallagher Transfer, Incorporated, 1982-1988; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Gallea Transfer and Storage, Incorporated, 1996-1999; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Gamble Robinson Company [1/2], 1979-1983; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Gamble Robinson Company [2/2], 1976-1978; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1976-1984; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Gateway Foods [1/2], 1981-1991; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Gateway Foods [2/2], 1991-1994; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General Drivers and Helpers, 1964-1971; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - George A. Clark and Son, Incorporated, 1974-1977; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Gibson Trucking Company, 1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Gilmore Transfer, Incorporated, 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Glendenning Motorways, Incorporated, 1961-1976; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Golden Pantry, Incorporated [1/2], 1982-1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Golden Pantry, Incorporated [2/2], 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Greif Brothers Corporation, 1970-1988; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Griggs Beer Distributors, Incorporated, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Gross Common Carrier, Incorporated, 1987; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Grosslein Beverages, Incorporated, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Groves-Kelco, 1972; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Guaranteed Sand and Gravel [1/2], 1973-1981; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Guaranteed Sand and Gravel [2/2], 1961-1964; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - H. Brooks and Company, 1979-1991; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hall's Motor Transit, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hammond Transfer, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hankin Transportation, 1978-1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hawkins Chemical, Incorporated, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    General
    Note written on old folder: "When adding new members put in employee number (clock). If member doesn't know it, call Irv English at company."
  - Heartland Food Company [1/2], 1988-1994; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Heartland Food Company [2/2], 1990-2000; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Henry Lambert Trucking Company, 1977-1979; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - High Value Products Division of Beltmann North American Company, Incorporated, 1997-1999; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Highway, Railroad, and Heavy Construction Agreement, 1970-1978; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Holiday Stores, Incorporated, 1966-1973; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Home Gas Company, Incorporated, 1969-1972; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated, 1976-1989; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - I. Bachall Steel and Supply, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - I.T.T. Continental Baking Company [1/2], 1972-1996; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - I.T.T. Continental Baking Company [2/2], 1978-1981; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Indianhead Truck Line, Incorporated, 1973-1985; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Brands Corporation [1/2], 1996-2006; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Brands Corporation [2/2], 2006-2011; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Brands Corporation, Wonder/Hostess Division [1/2], 1996-2005; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Brands Corporation, Wonder/Hostess Division [2/2], 2005-2013; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Express, Incorporated, 1976-1978; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - J.H. Foods [1/2], 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - J.H. Foods [2/2], 1980; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Jacobson Transfer Company, 1972-1985; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Janesville Auto Transport Company [1/2], 1977-1988; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Janesville Auto Transport Company [2/2], 1987; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Jenniges Transfer Company, 1971-1985; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jerome Foods, Incorporated, 1992-1994; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jerry's Foods, Incorporated, 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - John Sexton and Company, 1970-1979; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - John Warner d/b/a DJW Cartage, 1979; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Johnson Van and Storage Company, 1978-1985; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Johnston Furniture Transfer, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - KNUJ/KXLP, Incorporated, 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Karp's Twin City Supply, 1970-1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kato Movers and Storage Company [1/2], 1978-2000; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kato Movers and Storage Company [2/2], 1982-1983; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Kelly Transfer, Incorporated, 1975; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ken Page Transfer Company, Incorporated, 1994-1998; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Kenosha Auto Transport Company, 1977-1982; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Key City Oil Company/Phillips Petroleum Company, 1970-1971; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Knutson Trucking Company, 1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Kreutzer Motor Express, 1968-1971; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Kuhn's Moving and Storage, Incorporated, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - L.C.L. Transit Company [1/2], 1967-1970; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - L.C.L. Transit Company [2/2], 1967; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - L.L. Distribution Systems, Incorporated, 1976-1978; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - L.L. LeJuene Steel Company/Rocket Transfer, 1975; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - LaBelle Storage and Moving Company, 1979-1985; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - LaHarve Transfer Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - LaSalle Cartage Company, Incorporated, 1974-1988; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Labor Services Company, 1982-1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lake State Transport, Incorporated, 1980-1983; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Land O'Lakes, Incorporated, 1981-1987; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Landry Transfer, Incorporated, 1984; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Landy Packing Company, 1979-1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Larson Warehouse, 1979-1991; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lewis Truck Line, Incorporated, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Linderholm Trucking, Incorporated, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Lindsay Brothers Company, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Liquid Carbonic Carbon Dioxide Corporation [1/2], 1989-1994; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Liquid Carbonic Carbon Dioxide Corporation [2/2], 1992-1998; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Little Falls Wholesale Grocers, Incorporated, 1972-1973; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Livestock Service, Incorporated, 1974-1980; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Loomis Courier Service, 1970-1977; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ludwig-Lockhart Company, 1967-1976; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Lull Engineering Company, Incorporated, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lundin Construction Company, 1973-1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Luxton Truck Line, 1981-1988; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - M.F. Bank and Company, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - M&R Paving and Excavating, Incorporated, 1993-1996; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - MacMillan Bloedel Building Materials, 1997; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Madison Lutheran Home, Incorporated, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Maiers Transfer and Storage [1/2], 1973-1985; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Maiers Transfer and Storage [2/2], 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Main Express Company, 1981; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Malat-Katzmarek, Incorporated, 1979-1984; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Mankato Plating Company, 1977-1982; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Marigold Foods, Incorporated/Marigold Dairies [1/4], 1974-1977; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Marigold Foods, Incorporated/Marigold Dairies [2/4], 1977-1986; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Marigold Foods, Incorporated/Marigold Dairies [3/4], 1987-1994; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Marigold Foods, Incorporated/Marigold Dairies [4/4], 1995-2001; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Marigold Foods, Incorporated, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Mark VII Distributors, Incorporated, 1991-1994; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Market Companies, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Includes: Bergin Fruit Company, Bix Fruit Company, H. Brooks Company, Famous Foods/No. Country Poultry, Gamble-Robinson Company, Mike Handler Produce Company, Malat-Katzmarek, Incorporated, Perry Myers, Incorporated, Northwest Produce Company, Twin Cities Produce Supplies, Wholesale Produce Supply, Zuccaro's Produce
  - Marse Transfer, 1964-1967; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Masonite Corporation Distribution Center, 1982-1985; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Master Dairy Agreement [1/2], 1961-1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Master Dairy Agreement [2/2], 1972-2013; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Master Transfer Company, 1981-1985; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - May Brothers Company, 1967-1982; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - McKesson Chemical Company, 1977-1983; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Menning Transfer, 1961-1973; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Merchants Refridgerating Company, 1976-1987; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Mercury Motor Freight, Incorporated, 1973-1976; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Metal-Matic, Incorporated, 1975-1988; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Metcalf Moving and Storage Company, 1973-2000; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Contract Services, Incorporated, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Transfermen's Association, 1970-1973; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Metz Baking Company, 1984-1997; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Midland Cooperatives, Incorporated, 1965-1983; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Midwest Drivers Corporation, 1975-1997; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Midwest Employers Labor Advisory Council, Incorporated, 1978; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Midwest Machinery Movers, Incorporated, 1977; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Midwest Merchandise Mart, 1979; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Midwest Wine Company, Incorporated, 1958-1961; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Mike Handler Fruit and Produce Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Milwaukee Motor Transportation Company, 1979; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Minneapolis and St. Paul Milk Dealers, 1995-1999; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Minneapolis Automobile Dealers' Association, 1977-1980; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industries, 1967-1972; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Includes: Red Owl Stores, Incorporated, May Company, National Foods, Incorporated, Super Valu, Incorporated